Roy Justus Papers
Roy Justus Papers
- Artwork
  - By Justus
    - 1959 Jul-Dec, 131 items (Oversize 25)
      Jul 1: Katzenjammer kids
      Jul 2: Summit meeting
      Jul 3: Just when it seemed all finished out
      Jul 6: Can you walk a little closer to me?
      Jul 7: Did I do that?
      Jul 8: Chronic but not fatal
      Jul 9: Contr011ed by one little gadget
      Jul 10: To whom it may concern
      Jul 11: Fly-swatter
      Jul 13: Negotiating under difficulties
      Jul 14: Here we go again
      Jul 15: A would-be tourist sees America
      Jul 16: Fished out?
      Jul 17: You fellows better keep talking!
      Jul 18: Still looks very promising
      Jul 18: Hitchhiker
      Jul 19: The second big board
      Jul 20: See?
      Jul 21: They must think there's gold there!
      Jul 22: At long last
      Jul 23: Eternal vigilance
      Jul 24: Wonder what's going on in there!
      Jul 25: The way of the police state
      Jul 27: To the storm cellar
      Jul 28: Still in the kitchen
      Jul 29: Things are looking up!
      Jul 30: Hope this does not go to his head!
      Jul 31: As elusive as flying saucers
      Aug 1: The mountain labored
      Aug 3: ..and now he has the invitation
      Aug 4: Gosh-could this cause a flood?
      Aug 5: The intermediary
      Aug 6: Will it come to this?
      Aug 7: One summit to avoid
      Aug 8: A William Tell shot
      Aug 10: Ice or granite
      Aug 11: The soothsayer
      Aug 12: Good morning gentlemen!
      Aug 13: Seems to be something of a thaw
      Aug 14: Points of interest
      Aug 15: On the legislative golf course
      Aug 17: Political totem pole
      Aug 18: Watching for that wisp of smoke
      Aug 19: Studying the road map
      Aug 20: Segregated
      Aug 21: The steel picture
      Aug 22: Asking for trouble
      Aug 24: The anachronism
      Aug 25: We'd better take a little vacation!
      Aug 26: Reassuring our allies
      Aug 27: When you're preparing for a trip
      Aug 28: Adlai's faithful little lamb
      Aug 29: Is Mao chef..or cook's helper?
      Aug 30: The logical poll-taker
      Aug 31: At home and abroad
      Sep 1: Mao's garden
      Sep 2: Treading on eggs
      Sep 3: What about this inflation
      Sep 4: Trying to jettison the bomb
      Sep 5: An old army custom
      Sep 7: What did you say?
      Sep 8: Is this responsible government
      Sep 9: Detecting aggression used to be easy
      Sep 10: Mr. K's summit
      Sep 11: What big teeth you've, grandma!
      Sep 12: Well, Sam?
      Sep 14: What a spectacular entrance
      Sep 15: Gloomy prospects for the moon
      Sep 16: Removing the fuse is a two-man job
      Sep 17: The one most concerned
      Sep 18: The subject of disarmament may...come up most any time
      Sep 19: ..and have a good time
      Sep 21: The packed gallery
      Sep 22: Beginning to feel the weight
      Sep 23: Vacation note to the Kremlin
      Sep 24: Looking for the summit
      Sep 25: An interested bystander
      Sep 26: Well?
      Sep 28: The tourist season isn't over!
      Sep 29: He'll be tied up for sometime!
      Sep 30: Do you have a green thumb?
      Oct 1: It's almost unanimous
      Oct 2: The hot potato he left behind
      Oct 3: Great American debate
      Oct 5: Which is he trying to impress most?
      Oct 6: Shocking sound from outer space
      Oct 7: America's science lab
      Oct 8: Holding the boy
      Oct 9: Two spheres
      Oct 10: Reading the tea leaves
      Oct 12: Hey-nix on the fireworks!
      Oct 13: Wanted: a good road map
      Oct 14: He can't just ignore it
      Oct 15: Space frontier just in time!
      Nov 10: Is the tail wagging the dog
      Nov 13: The voluntary bath
      Nov 14: Will he take advantage of this summit?
      Nov 16: The hard sell
      Nov 17: Highly experimental mating
      Nov 18: Destiny, no doubt, decrees it!
      Nov 20: In the rockets' red glare
      Nov 23: Change of posture
      Nov 24: The third force
      Nov 25: No caption
      Nov 26: In orbit
      Nov 27: King Canute
      Nov 28: Making progress
      Nov 30: Above and beyond the call of duty
      Dec 1: Super sputnik
      Dec 2: The compact trailer
      Dec 3: The 18th hole is a lulu!
      Dec 5: Revising it!
      Dec 7: The modern Cinderella
      Dec 10: The ever-ready executioner
      Dec 11: Wonder, what is in the bag!
      Dec 12: Mistletoe
      Dec 14: Must be the rarefied atmosphere
      Dec 15: And they said it couldn't be done
      Dec 16: The face at the window
      Dec 17: If talk could kill I'd be dead!
      Dec 18: The heavy hand
      Dec 19: Trying to get into the act
      Dec 20: It's only a dream of course
      Dec 21: Stubborn stork
      Dec 22: ...and a happy new year
      Dec 23: We've found the abominable snowman
      Dec 24: Welcome home!
      Dec 25: The voice of America
      Dec 26: Waiting for the cue
      Dec 28: The dictator's solution
      Dec 29: 1960 convention detail
      Dec 30: Not much progress
    - 1960 Jan-Jun, 131 items (Oversize 26)
      Jan 1: Each entrance becomes more dazzling
      Jan 2: Our own 1960 prediction
      Jan 4: Step on it!
      Jan 5: The enlarged forum
      Jan 6: It's Goliath's shield that troubles David
      Jan 8: Congress gets down to business
      Jan 9: Firing up
      Jan 11: The reluctant astronaut
      Jan 13: About to be another lynching
      Jan 15: The old ringmaster
      Jan 16: Disarmament?
      Jan 18: Have you noticed the moon lately
      Jan 19: Setting the election campaign tone?
      Jan 20: Persuasive platform
      Jan 21: A long way from Pearl Harbour and Hiroshima
      Jan 22: What about me?
      Jan 25: This is no phony act
      Jan 26: The ordeal
      Jan 27: No caption
      Jan 27: Will it come to this
      Jan 28: Hello! Whiskers!
      Jan 29: The game is more dangerous than ever
      Jan 30: The bee
      Feb 1: Remarkable mutation
      Feb 2: Beating swords into missiles
      Feb 3: Race to break the stalemate
      Feb 4: Wind or rain clouds?
      Feb 5: The plight of humpty dumpty
      Feb 5: Isn't this drug awfully expensive
      Feb 8: Company's coming
      Feb 9: Our first astronaut
      Feb 11: At the wishing well
      Feb 12: Who says tourism is dead in Cuba?
      Feb 13: This could lead to something
      Feb 15: Getting old
      Feb 16: Ready for talks with Mr. K and the west
      Feb 17: The side show
      Feb 18: Here we go again!
      Feb 19: Direct hit!
      Feb 20: New textbook
      Feb 22: Crescendo
      Feb 23: Still in training
      Feb 25: You don't dare lay a hand on me!
      Feb 26: When the doctors disagree
      Feb 27: Lost in the jungle
      Feb 29: That slender thread
      Mar 1: The evangelist
      Mar 2: Do you have a road map?
      Mar 3: Nothing like warmed-over stew
      Mar 4: Who leads in this missile race?
      Mar 5: There'll be a slight delay
      Mar 7: The Cuban sugar bowl
      Mar 8: Hope springs eternal
      Mar 9: Would you repeat that, please?
      Mar 10: No caption
      Mar 11: Bull market
      Mar 12: Prestige vehicle
      Mar 14: You're under arrest - come with me!
      Mar 15: The law of gravity or something
      Mar 16: Climate control
      Mar 17: Uncle, your gap is showing
      Mar 18: Damn yanks!
      Mar 19: Is it an oak?
      Mar 21: In orbit
      Mar 22: Permanent chairman
      Mar 24: Very interesting!'
      Mar 25: There - that's more becoming!
      Mar 26: Three quarters of a loaf...
      Mar 28: Could this be a sign of spring?
      Mar 29: May be they didn't invest it, but they certainly perfected it!
      Mar 30: Somebody may get hurt
      Mar 31: Somewhere just hibernating
      Apr 1: Foot in the door
      Apr 2: Richard!
      Apr 4: New battle of the air waves?
      Apr 5: Where you guys think you're going?
      Apr 6: Cheese testing
      Apr 6: A light that casts darkness
      Apr 7: Who's the adult in the background?
      Apr 9: No caption
      Apr 12: Isn't there a cool surplus already?
      Apr 13: Dangerous performance
      Apr 14: How to cut the pie?
      Apr 15: Mash note
      Apr 16: When is a candidate not a candidate?
      Apr 17: Getting in shape for the summit
      Apr 18: Dirty little interlopers!
      Apr 19: He loves me - he loves me not -
      Apr 20: Summit preparations
      Apr 20: Which way are the GOP winds blowing?
      Apr 21: Spreading democracy in the orient
      Apr 23: This kind of fall-out is heavy, too!
      Apr 25: Do you hear a trumpet?
      Apr 25: Some folks are still skeptical
      Apr 26: Love me, love my dog!
      Apr 28: Still a little awkward in the saddle
      Apr 29: Cloud bigger than a man's head
      May 2: Dubious honor
      May 3: The rush is on
      May 4: Another boy at the dike
      May 5: Could this be the millennium?
      May 6: A hard sell
      May 7: Trails and tribulations of a summit
      May 9: Coal miner
      May 10: Slight revision
      May 11: Special delivery, too!
      May 12: One sign suggests another
      May 13: Summit exhibits a & b
      May 14: I've a feeling I'm being watched!
      May 16: Which will be the summit mascot?
      May 17: Making a molehill out of a mountain
      May 18: Powerful dictator or puppet?
      May 19: What happened?
      May 20: From one summit to another
      May 21: The wall that Nikita built
      May 23: Testing its political potency
      May 24: May be I can still get in the act!
      May 25: Who said the summit was a failure?
      May 26: Age of the common man
      May 27: Watch your step, dick
      May 28: Let's keep politics out of this!
      May 30: This hurts you more than me
      May 31: Which is the real target?
      Jun 1: The grandfather clock
      Jun 2: Now, if I were to make a choice!
      Jun 3: Some folks are still skeptical
      Jun 4: Dangerous bull market
      Jun 6: Any time now
      Jun 28: The damn comes up like thunder...
      Jun 29: It's in the bag!
      Jun 30: No caption
    - 1960 Jul-Dec, 151 items (Oversize 27)
      Jul 1: The hobnails are getting bigger
      Jul 2: No caption
      Jul 4: You can always depend on harry!
      Jul 5: Adding something to the act
      Jul 6: Will it have to come to this?
      Jul 7: As perennial as election
      Jul 8: Summits are a precarious business
      Jul 11: Strange, so many want to occupy it!
      Jul 11: Four up
      Jul 12: The fight is on
      Jul 13: The band wagon
      Jul 14: Unfavorable circus weather
      Jul 14: Convention balloon
      Jul 18: People to people
      Jul 19: Hey - a little less noise over there!
      Jul 20: The presidents briefing section
      Jul 21: The cat in gloves
      Jul 22: Who's circling whom?
      Jul 23: Another one?
      Jul 25: One of them will be our reader
      Jul 26: Great Chicago fire, 1960
      Jul 28: Losing locket
      Jul 29: Technology waits for no man
      Jul 30: Anyone dare call him weak now?
      Aug 1: Uncharted course
      Aug 2: Grist for the legislative mill
      Aug 3: Those farm hands again
      Aug 4: African vulture
      Aug 5: Off to the political wars
      Aug 7: The battleground
      Aug 8: Gentlemen, choose your weapon
      Aug 9: Fresh from the conventions!
      Aug 10: Lost in the political jungle
      Aug 11: Wonder when the campaign starts
      Aug 12: The big TV debate is all set
      Aug 13: Looking for the lost Sister Kenny funds
      Aug 15: Whe-e-e-e!
      Aug 16: Playful Nikita
      Aug 17: Help
      Aug 18: The missionary
      Aug 19: Now let's see what is our most pressing problem?
      Aug 20: Capitol hill archery
      Aug 22: Ah, senor - free elections are grand!
      Aug 23: It droppeth as the gentle rain from heaven
      Aug 24: Hope springs eternal
      Aug 26: The nest
      Aug 28: Who is king of the beasts?
      Aug 29: Where is your party loyalty?
      Aug 30: Uncle Sam's melon patch
      Aug 31: And may the best man win!
      Sep 1: What's going on there, comrade?
      Sep 2: Headed for the political hustings
      Sep 3: Khrushchev is coming!
      Sep 5: Cramped quarters
      Sep 6: I don't think they're ready for self-government
      Sep 7: Business is picking up
      Sep 8: Ho-hum!
      Sep 9: A little too neighborly!
      Sep 10: Back to school
      Sep 12: Here comes the peace-maker!
      Sep 13: Unwelcome campaigner
      Sep 14: This would be the last straw!
      Sep 15: John q. Voter in two poses
      Sep 16: More than casual interest
      Sep 17: Phew! - what a responsibility!
      Sep 19: The band wagon
      Sep 20: Shouting is better than shooting
      Sep 21: The mouse and the elephant
      Sep 22: Not according to plans
      Sep 23: Don't you think we ought to try again?
      Sep 24: The Russian bear speaks
      Sep 26: Static
      Sep 27: If I can't have you nobody else can!
      Sep 28: The winner!
      Sep 29: Bringing home the quarry
      Sep 30: Always at the summit
      Oct 1: Mr. K. Offers a change in the U.N.
      Oct 3: Wonder what makes Ike's so wary?
      Oct 4: Campaign buttons
      Oct 5: If it isn't one thing it's another!
      Oct 6: It's a cruel world
      Oct 7: Watch it, Fidel!
      Oct 8: Waiting for the cue
      Oct 9: He huffs and he puffs
      Oct 10: Who'll win this debate?
      Oct 11: United ostriches in session
      Oct 12: The retreat to Moscow
      Oct 13: Cast your ballot today
      Oct 14: They're talking about us!
      Oct 15: Still another execution
      Oct 17: Wow - things are looking up!
      Oct 18: Off on a non-political trip
      Oct 19: The home stretch is always roughest
      Oct 20: Neck and neck
      Oct 21: Uncle Sam's prestige abroad
      Oct 22: Still a little blurred!
      Oct 24: When a feller needs a friend
      Oct 25: Bringing up the heavies
      Oct 26: The undecided voter
      Oct 27: Speaking of prestige
      Oct 28: The pollster's headache
      Oct 29: Stuck record
      Oct 31: Finger painting
      Nov 1: Is red china reconsidering?
      Nov 2: No caption
      Nov 3: The lively corpse
      Nov 4: Elections in Cuba, too!
      Nov 5: Is roughing illegal
      Nov 7: Prize for the winner
      Nov 8: Any doubt of our endurance?
      Nov 9: Just a bump!
      Nov 10: Another winner!
      Nov 11: The new atlas
      Nov 12: Jack's charger
      Nov 14: This baby goes with the white house
      Nov 15: Is that cigar habit spreading?
      Nov 16: It's crowded up here!
      Nov 18: Hey - Charlie, Mac, Konrad...
      Nov 19: On the subject of education
      Nov 21: Now watch this
      Nov 22: Who says the election is over?
      Nov 23: Changing administration
      Nov 24: A rose is a rose is a rose...
      Nov 25: Not very effective
      Nov 26: But it's fun!
      Nov 28: The ex-philanthropist
      Nov 29: This is where I came in!
      Nov 30: The winner is Louisiana
      Dec 1: The pigeon shoot
      Dec 2: Havana cigar
      Dec 3: Initiating the new golfer
      Dec 5: Infernal combination
      Dec 6: The lesson for to-day
      Dec 7: Just like new!
      Dec 8: Striking a blow for liberty
      Dec 9: Now they're both pointing!
      Dec 10: Destination unknown
      Dec 12: The cabinet maker
      Dec 13: Santa's competitor
      Dec 14: The geographer
      Dec 15: The east and the west have met
      Dec 16: Lucky you...it's all yours!
      Dec 19: All set!
      Dec 20: The balanced rock
      Dec 21: Dear Santa...
      Dec 22: Steady or shifting?
      Dec 23: The leader
      Dec 24: Editor for the day
      Dec 27: Almost as big as Texas
      Dec 28: Here comes another one!
      Dec 30: Another new calendar...
    - 1961 Jan-Jun, 144 items (Oversize 28)
      Jan 2: Redecorating the dome
      Jan 3: Tomorrow's jungle
      Jan 4: Abominable snow-man again
      Jan 5: See no evil-hear no evil!
      Jan 6: You're a bad old boy!
      Jan 7: To john f. Kennedy...
      Jan 9: The long vigil
      Jan 10: Ready - go!
      Jan 11: That's your ball, jack!
      Jan 12: To the victor belong the spoils
      Jan 13: I don't think it's getting smaller!
      Jan 14: Divided opinion
      Jan 16: What's wrong comrade?
      Jan 17: The younger generation gets a lecture
      Jan 18: Smoldering
      Jan 19: Pardon me!
      Jan 20: The new leader-must be crazy...
      Jan 21: Inviting target
      Jan 23: The jigsaw puzzle
      Jan 24: Yeah...let bygones be bygones!
      Jan 25: No caption
      Jan 29: Hands across the sea
      Jan 30: Red carpet treatment
      Feb 1: An old frontier
      Feb 2: Very much alive
      Feb 3: What is it?
      Feb 4: At your service, sir!
      Feb 5: It's an ill wind
      Feb 6: Oriental influence
      Feb 7: Needed dexterity
      Feb 8: The blotch
      Feb 9: The sphinx might know, but...
      Feb 10: Wait a minute, young fellow!
      Feb 11: Missile gap of the future
      Feb 13: Here's your new outfit, podner!
      Feb 14: The new frontier
      Feb 15: One for the road
      Feb 17: What's all the nonsense?
      Feb 18: Who's ahead in the missile race?
      Feb 20: No matter how you slice it...
      Feb 21: Egg heads
      Feb 22: Busy fire department
      Feb 23: He may be a bit tardy
      Feb 24: Here's that frontier!
      Feb 25: Dangerous bulwark
      Feb 27: The rock
      Mar 1: Can I give you a lift?
      Mar 2: Hobnailed missionary
      Mar 3: Mary's lamb again
      Mar 4: They don't dare stop trying
      Mar 6: Book burner extraordinary
      Mar 8: Urgent invitation to learning
      Mar 9: Gentlemen, be seated!
      Mar 10: Democracy in action
      Mar 11: The first ice age was a minor incident
      Mar 13: When the doctors disagree
      Mar 14: That's not my egg!
      Mar 15: Better late than never
      Mar 16: Isn't this sort of risky
      Mar 17: Out on the old frontier
      Mar 18: Russia's secret weapon
      Mar 20: To-day's hot ones
      Mar 21: That ol' rock of Gibraltar
      Mar 23: Please - someone take me to my leader!
      Mar 24: Disarmament conference
      Mar 25: Refrigerator salesman
      Mar 27: Where it would rest most heavily
      Mar 28: Fragile flower
      Mar 29: The axman
      Mar 30: Dis sort o' thing raises my status!
      Mar 31: Did you call, sir?
      Apr 1: Strange bedfellows
      Apr 3: Running wild again
      Apr 4: Working in the shadows
      Apr 5: Hardly a dignified posture
      Apr 6: Matching skills
      Apr 7: Why?
      Apr 8: Conference? - sure! - after dinner!
      Apr 10: The die-hard
      Apr 11: Problems of leadership
      Apr 12: Might make a world of difference
      Apr 13: Wonder if the cosmonaut noticed!
      Apr 14: Whoa, boy - don't panic!
      Apr 15: Book-of-the-month - once again!
      Apr 17: I'll be when you return!
      Apr 18: Twin victories
      Apr 19: Spreading!
      Apr 20: Where is the target?
      Apr 21: Sure-fire action
      Apr 22: It certainly was loaded
      Apr 24: Inter-planetary travel can't come too soon!
      Apr 25: Pointed!
      Apr 26: E-e-e-ek!
      Apr 27: Quiet!
      Apr 28: What kind of frontier is dis?
      Apr 29: Could cover a multitude of sins
      May 1: Wash your hands first, Fidel!
      May 2: No place to hide
      May 3: ...and more to come!
      May 4: Here's one for all Americans!
      May 5: Still very, very, groggy
      May 6: The recovery
      May 8: What lousy fishin'!
      May 9: Keep your squabbling to yourselves!
      May 10: The highest of futility
      May 11: Which hand do you pick...the right or the left?
      May 12: Pity the poor scapegoat
      May 15: On and on and on
      May 16: Getting higher and higher
      May 18: Inflation
      May 19: Delirium tremens
      May 20: The continuing challenge
      May 22: Has anybody seen our canary?
      May 23: ...good and faithful servant
      May 24: Heady stuff
      May 25: Sometimes I even hate myself!
      May 26: Literally speaking
      May 27: Comrade Nikita
      May 29: Damned communist!
      May 30: Two basketfuls
      May 31: Summit bound
      Jun 1: Part of the new frontier
      Jun 2: Smoldering
      Jun 3: And on the home-front
      Jun 5: See?...it's easy!
      Jun 6: Back to work
      Jun 7: Well - hello there!
      Jun 8: How are you boys coming up there?
      Jun 12: Treacherous head winds
      Jun 13: Cold war arsenal
      Jun 14: Will Uncle Sam come to this?
      Jun 15: Crucial summit
      Jun 16: Labor saving technology?
      Jun 17: The mountain of granite
      Jun 19: Dangerous hunter
      Jun 21: Will junior heed the call?
      Jun 22: Fruit for Nikita
      Jun 24: All smiles
      Jun 26: Portrait of the new beatnik
      Jun 27: Torture chamber
      Jun 28: How'd I get off the turn pike?
      Jun 29: Hasn't quite registered yet!
      Jun 30: Two minds with a single thought
    - 1961 Jul-Dec, 130 items (Oversize 29)
      Jul 1: Strange way to fight communism
      Jul 4: Four - three - two - one!?
      Jul 5: Victim of highway slaughter
      Jul 6: Say when!
      Jul 7: Testing the winds
      Jul 8: Open-up..or close!
      Jul 10: What a wonderful invention
      Jul 11: Somebody call King Solomon
      Jul 12: What an exciting future
      Jul 13: How strong the shield?
      Jul 14: Maybe he has developed immunity
      Jul 15: Carrying water on both shoulders
      Jul 17: Perfect soil for communist seed
      Jul 18: Old faithful
      Jul 19: The one-way street
      Jul 20: Our educational race with Russia
      Jul 21: Shades of Adolf Hitler
      Jul 22: Handicap race
      Jul 24: The age of reason
      Jul 25: One backache after another
      Jul 26: Referee boning up!
      Jul 27: Received and answered
      Jul 28: Immovable object - irresistible force
      Jul 29: How patient is the patient old hen?
      Jul 31: Conventional warfare, revised
      Aug 1: West European integration
      Aug 2: Whoa!
      Aug 3: Double trouble
      Aug 4: The Kremlin's new space triumph
      Aug 5: Must he get the fly swatter?
      Aug 6: Much talk - little action
      Aug 7: Look out behind
      Aug 8: Cosmonaut still in orbit
      Aug 10: Watch it, jumbo!
      Aug 11: Speaking from-a vantage point
      Aug 12: The lady and the dragon
      Aug 13: He and his shadow
      Aug 14: Crazy birds!
      Aug 16: ...that is the question
      Aug 17: Stews are his specialty
      Aug 18: Perpetual backache
      Aug 19: Those blasted Yankee tunes
      Sep 13: Mightier than the pen
      Sep 14: His greatest woes are self inflicted
      Sep 15: The last word in bombs
      Sep 16: The squeeze
      Sep 18: Time for a shave or something
      Sep 19: Dag Hammarskjold
      Sep 20: The thinker
      Sep 21: Now the devolution of man
      Sep 22: And now you!
      Sep 23: Squall or hurricane
      Sep 25: How to let go?
      Sep 26: The hope of mankind
      Sep 27: United nations menagerie
      Sep 28: Small comfort
      Sep 29: But the window is still open
      Sep 30: Up for a breath of fresh air
      Oct 2: Sea legs
      Oct 3: Critics from A to Z
      Oct 4: No caption
      Oct 5: I'm gettin' quite respectable!
      Oct 6: Bomb shelter
      Oct 9: Quick, somebody - a tranquilizer!
      Oct 10: Clarifying the fall-out dispute
      Oct 11: Plaything
      Oct 12: Modern head shrinker
      Oct 13: He prefers a little privacy
      Oct 14: Why don't you fellows cool off?
      Oct 16: It's a cruel world
      Oct 17: The fourth wheel
      Oct 18: I was just foolin'!
      Oct 19: It begins at home
      Oct 20: The greatest cosmonaut of them all
      Oct 21: Tweedledum and Tweedledee...
      Oct 23: The privileged and the unprivileged
      Oct 24: Literary critic
      Oct 25: Prelude to what
      Oct 26: More fall-out
      Oct 27: Activity on the home front
      Oct 30: The reserves
      Oct 31: Last of the series
      Nov 1: Fifty megaton fall out
      Nov 2: I just don't like compacts!